&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们试着澄清一些关于继承的想法，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's try to clarify some ideas around inheritance, okay?
因为我向你扔了很多东西
Because there is a lot of things that I've thrown at you and
我只想尽可能清晰地画出一个可视化的图表。
I just wanna make as clear sort of a visual diagram as I can.
在经典的面向语言中，C+，Java，诸如此类的东西。
In classical oriented Languages C++, Java, stuff like that.
当您进行类调用工作坊并实例化它时，您在概念上是
When you make a class call workshop and you instantiate it, you are conceptually
在某些情况下，物理复制到这些实例中。
and in some cases, physically copying down into those instances.
当你让一个孩子班呼叫另一个扩展车间的车间时，
And when you make a child class call another workshop that extends workshop,
你是在复制到那里面。
you are copying down into that.
当您实例化那个子类时。
And when you instantiate that child class.
你在复印更多。
You're doing more copies.
换句话说，这些箭头是从左到右，从上到下，
So in other words these arrows are going from left to right, top to bottom,
因为它们基本上是复制操作。
because they are fundamentally copy operations.
当您尝试进行原型继承时，您有一个workshop.prototype对象。
When you try to do prototypal inheritance, you have a workshop.prototype object.
然后你制作另一个物体，比如Deep JS或
And then you make another object like deepJS or
reactJS，这些对象链接到Workshop.prototype。
reactJS, those objects are linked to Workshop.prototype.
然后当你制作另一个工作区时，它会被链接到Prototype。
And then when you make another workshop.prototype it is linked to.
然后，当您创建JSRecentParts时，它也会被链接。
And then when you make JSRecentParts it is linked too.
所以在这里，箭头从右到左，从下到上。
So here, the arrows go from right to left, and bottom to top.
因为这是一个链接，而不是一个拷贝。
Because this is a linkage, not a copy.
跟我来。
Follow me.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这通常被称为原型继承。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This is often to referred to as prototypal inheritance.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我有很深的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have a deep,
把这称为原型继承的想法是一个令人不安的问题。
troubling issue with the idea of calling this prototypal inheritance.
这就是我的问题所在。
And here is what my issue is.
对于必须的人来说，原型这个词甚至没有任何具体的含义。
The word prototypal doesn't even really mean anything concrete to must people.
甚至没有人真正知道那是什么意思。
Nobody even really knows what that means.
他们只是把它和这个奇怪的系统联系起来。
They just associate it with this strange system.
但是继承这个词有很强的含义，它承载着很多包袱。
But the word inheritance has a very strong meaning, it carries lots of baggage.
大多数人的大脑都被编程来考虑遗传，
And most people's brains have been programmed to think about inheritance,
因为有复制关系。
as having copy relationships.
所以我们所做的就是把这个令人困惑的声音
So what we did was we took this confusing-sounding
花哨的词就像原型一样，把它放在另一个词的前面。
fancy word like prototypal, stuck it in front of another word.
然后我们假装这没问题，完全颠倒了它的意义。
And then we pretended as if that's okay, to completely reverse the meaning of it.
就好像我站在你面前，一只手拿着一个苹果，然后
It's as if I stood up in front of you and I had an apple in one hand, and
另一个是橙子。
an orange in the other.
然后我说，不，那不是苹果。
And then I said, no, no, no that's not an apple.
那只是一个红色的橙子。
That's just a red orange.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：你看着我就像，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You'd look at me like,
你管它叫什么都不会改变它的本来面目。
what you call it doesn't change what it is.
是苹果对吧？
It's an apple, right?
你所说的这并不能改变它的本质。
What you call this doesn't change what it is.
这只会造成更多的混乱。
It only creates more confusion.
20多年来，JavaScript开发人员一直感到困惑
For 20 plus years JavaScript developers have been confused
为什么JavaScript中的类不起作用。
by why don't classes in JavaScript work.
就像他们在其他语言中做的那样，似乎没有人有勇气
The way they do in other languages, and nobody seems to have had the courage
告诉他们，这是因为系统完全不同。
to tell them, it's because the systems are completely fundamentally different.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：在某种意义上，我们一直在迎合情感依恋
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We've been, in a sense, pandering to the emotional attachment
添加到类设计模式中，并在
to the class design pattern and adding extra complexity on top of
适合语法糖设计者的JavaScript。
JavaScript to suit the syntactic sugar designers.
而不是仅仅拥抱JavaScript已经是什么。
Instead of just embracing what JavaScript already is.
拥抱其原型系统，拥抱动态这一性质。
Embracing its prototype system, embracing the dynamic this nature.
我们一直在尝试把所有其他的东西放在上面，这样它就可以成为一个类
We keep trying to put all these other things on it so that it can be a class
系统，该死的，它绝对是类，而实际上它不是类。
system, dang it, it's definitely classes, and in reality it's not classes.
只是我们想做得更好
It's just we're trying to do a better and
更好的工作，管道胶带它看起来像班级。
better job of duct taping it to look like classes.